Guide to the David T. Mason Papers 1865-2004
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Theatre, 1970-1998; Series III
  - Scripts, 1986-1998; Subseries 2
    - "Out of This World", undated (Box-folder 8/13)
    - "Drums in the Night", undated (Box-folder 8/14)
    - "With music by Kurt Weill", 1978 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - "Edward II", 1982 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - "Crisis at Middlesex Ranch", 1986 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - "Blue Baroque" - with Director's notebook and script mock-ups, 1991 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - "Woyzeck", 1993 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - "Gilgamesh", circa 1998 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Compositions, circa 1981-1998; Subseries 3
    - Composition notebook, 1981 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - "The Last Love of Lucifer", 1981 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - "I Might Have Been a Star", 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - "Whirligig", 1989 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - "Gilgamesh", 1998 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Compositions for clarinet, undated (Box-folder 8/26)
  - Photographs, 1977-1990s; Subseries 4
    - "Trial by Jury", 1974 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - "The Yeoman of the Guard" (includes costume notebook), 1979 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - "The Persecution and Assassination of Jean-Paul Marat", circa 1980 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - "Gondoliers", 1980 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - "The Sorceror", 1981 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - "Edward II", 1982 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - "Utopia", 1983 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - "The Last Love of Lucifer", 1985 (Box-folder 8/34)
    - "Crisis at Middlesex Ranch", 1986 (Box-folder 8/35)
    - "Princess Ida", undated (Box-folder 8/36)
    - "Patience", 1998 (Box-folder 8/37)
    - "The Mikado", undated (Box-folder 9/1)
    - "Tommy" - student-directed production, undated (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Unknown plays and performances/theatre events, undated (Box-folder 9/3)
    - "Some Awful Brecht Thing", undated (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Recordings - Film, undated; Subseries 5
    - "Goroka" - six reels, undated (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Recordings - Sound, 1979 December 22; Subseries 6
    - "Mahogany Live at the Met", 1979 December 22 (Box-folder 9/7)
- Writings and Art, 1960-1997; Series IV
  - Poetry, Prose, and Compositions, circa 1960-1997; Subseries 1
    - Musical compositions, 1964-1990 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Philosophical writings on science, art, and the environment, circa 1969-1995 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Poetry, 1955-1984 (Box-folder 9/10-9/11)
    - "Stories from a Life", undated (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Publications, self and local, 1990; 1993; 1997 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Drawings, undated; Subseries 2
    - Drawings by David T. Mason, undated (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Prints by Stephen McMillan, undated (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Collected Publications, 1975; 1980; Subseries 3
    - "Morning Due: Voices of Anti-sexist Men", 1975 March-April (Box-folder 9/16)
    - "Northwest Oasis: A Forum for Gay Culture", 1980 (Box-folder 9/17)